supload.com 2017-06-06

# Supload - Free image hosting that earns you bitcoin

#### General

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the [https://www.supload.com](https://www.supload.com/) and Supload, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Supload, Inc. include[https://www.supload.com](https://www.supload.com/) and Supload. The Supload website is a social media site. By using the Supload website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Use of your Personal Information

Supload collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Supload may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Supload and its affiliates. Supload may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Supload does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Supload may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Supload, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Supload may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Supload, in order to determine what Supload services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Supload to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Supload will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Supload or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Supload; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Supload, or the public.

#### Security of your Personal Information

Supload secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a bitcoin transaction) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Supload by contacting us here:

  * Web page: [https://www.supload.com](https://www.supload.com/)
  * Email: help@supload.com

#### Contact Information

Supload welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Supload has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Supload at:

Supload, Inc.  
6370 West Flamingo Road, Suite 12  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89103  

#### Collection of your Personal Information

Supload may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you utilize  Suploads products and services, we collect billing and payment information. This information is used to complete the payment transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Supload. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Supload website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Suploads public comment section, this information may be collected and used by others.

Supload encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Supload so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Supload is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Supload website.

#### Use of Cookies

The Supload website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Supload pages, or register with Supload site or services, a cookie helps Supload to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Supload website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Supload features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Supload services or websites you visit.

#### Children Under Thirteen

Supload does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Changes to this Statement

Supload will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Supload encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Supload is protecting your information.
